<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Koalacomk</title>
    <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Koalacomk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Koalacomk.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Clustering with R</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/06/22/2021-06-22-clustering-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/06/22/2021-06-22-clustering-with-r/</guid>
      <description>Clustering with R 
Cluster é uma técnica estatística não supervisionada de aglomeração ou agrupamento de elementos ou indíviduos dado suas características e semelhanças. Este agrupamento deve-se a distãncia euclidiana entre os indivíduos e pode ser classificada em Hierarquica e não Hierarquica. Neste post vamos demonstrar como utilizar o R para faze-lo, utilizando uma base de dados e 3 técnicas diferentes. Vamos falar da base primeiro.
 Cluster is an unsupervised statistical technique of grouping of elements or individuals considering their characteristics and similarities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pythonista Automation: Smart Switch</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/05/22/2021-05-22-pythonista-automation-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/05/22/2021-05-22-pythonista-automation-switch/</guid>
      <description>Pythonista / IOS Automations - Using a Switch 
One of the values that we as programmers look for is the practicality in our life, whether in our personal or professional life we always look for improvements of our activities. One of the issues sought in the market that impact our personal lives is the Smart house or Home Automation, which consists of automating or monitoring our domestic tasks and environments using internet connectivity and integrated systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>1. Who am i? Luiz Fernando de Lucena, 33 y/o Brazilian, living on Chile - Viña del Mar. My nickname is Koala (just in cause you didn&amp;rsquo;t notice) and i am a Geek enthusiast, i use to play A LOT of videogames and other geek stuffs. I like to travel (18 countries visited so far) but since Covid started i mainly ride my bike along the pacific Coast of Valparaiso.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
