<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Koalacomk</title>
    <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Koalacomk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Koalacomk.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Linear Regression</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/11/27/2021-11-27-multilinear-regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/11/27/2021-11-27-multilinear-regression/</guid>
      <description>What it is and how to use Linear Regression on R
PT: Se você nunca ouviu falar sobre o tema, regressão linear é uma análise preditiva supervisionada usada para entender e explicar a relação entre uma variável dependente com variáveis independentes. Isso significa que é um modelo ou uma fórmula que explica o comportamento de uma variável Y dadas variáveis X que impactam a variável Y.Digamos que queremos estudar o consumo de sorvete por dia em uma loja.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clustering with R</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/06/22/2021-06-22-clustering-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/06/22/2021-06-22-clustering-with-r/</guid>
      <description>How to classify education expenditure by country using clusters?
PT: Cluster é uma técnica estatística não supervisionada de aglomeração ou agrupamento de elementos ou indíviduos dado suas características e semelhanças. Este agrupamento deve-se a distãncia euclidiana entre os indivíduos e pode ser classificada em Hierarquica e não Hierarquica.Neste post vamos demonstrar como utilizar o R para faze-lo, utilizando uma base de dados e 3 técnicas diferentes. Vamos falar da base primeiro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pythonista Automation: Smart Switch</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/05/22/2021-05-22-pythonista-automation-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/blog/2021/05/22/2021-05-22-pythonista-automation-switch/</guid>
      <description>Pythonista / IOS Automations - Using a Switch
We,programmers, always seek for practicality in our life, whether in our personal or professional environment we always look for improvements of our daily activities. One of the main automation in the market that impact our personal lives is the Smart house or Home Automation, which consists of automating or monitoring our domestic tasks and environments using internet connectivity and integrated systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://Koalacomk.github.io/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Koalacomk.github.io/faq/</guid>
      <description>1. Who am i? Luiz Fernando de Lucena, 34 y/o Brazilian, living on Chile - Viña del Mar. My nickname is Koala (just in cause you didn&amp;rsquo;t noticed it ) and i am a Geek enthusiast, i use to play A LOT of videogames and others geek stuffs. I like to travel a lot (18 countries visited so far) but since Covid started i mainly ride my bike along the pacific Coast of Valparaiso.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
